truckingarticles.com 2012-05-04

# Privacy Policy

**Truckingarticles.com Privacy Policy**

**What information does Truckingarticles.com collect?**

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet. **Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the[Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy/ads/).**

Truckingarticles.com collects information from you when you fill out a CDL Training form. 

When filling out a form on Truckingarticles.com, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name, e-mail address, mailing address or phone number. **You may opt out of any newsletters by clicking the cancel link at the bottom of the page of any e-mail you receive.**

You may opt out of being contacted by trucking school represenatives after filling out a (Best CDL Training Form)by emailing [tjdude44@gmail.com](mailto:tjdude44@gmail.com) and stating that you wish to cancel. By submitting this form you are consenting that you may be contacted by a trucking school representative and/or receive periodic e-mail correspondence from Truckingarticles.com or an affiliate of cdlpracticetest.net. Truckingarticles.com may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

 **Third party links**

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

 **Online Privacy Policy Only**

This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.

**Your Consent**

By using Truckingarticles.com, you consent to our websites privacy policy. 

**Changes to our Privacy Policy**

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will update the Privacy Policy modification date below. 

This policy was last modified on 12/20/10

 **Truckingarticles.com Privacy Policy**

**Terms and Conditions -** This site is owned and operated by Truckingarticles.com. Your access and use of the Site is subject to the following terms and conditions on this page, and all applicable laws.

By accessing and browsing the Site, you accept, without limitation or qualification, the Terms and Conditions. If you do not agree with any of the below Terms and Conditions, do not use the Site and do not fill out any forms. Truckingarticles.com reserves the right, in its sole discretion, to modify, alter or otherwise update these Terms and Conditions at any time and by using our Site, you agree to be bound by such modifications, alterations or updates.

By filling out this form you give your consent to be contacted by e-mail or telephone by trucking school representatives! If you do not wish to be contacted by these trucking school representatives you agree to contact them directly, through e-mail cancellation links or phone and not Truckingarticles.com. Truckingarticles.com is not responsible for any statements or claims made by any trucking school. 

**© 2010-2011** Truckingarticles.com
